Harlan Fiske Stone Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Supreme Court File: General Office File, 1925-1944 (Box 80-82)
  - Bankruptcy in the Southern District of New York
    - 1929, Jan.-Feb.
    - 1929, Mar.
  - Bridges v. California, letters from the public, 1945
  - Clerk of the court
    - 1926-1928
    - 1929-1931
    - 1932-1934
    - 1935-1936
  - “Court packing plan,” letters from the public, 1937
  - Criticisms of the court, 1941-1944
  - Jones v. City of Opelika
    - Clippings, 1942-1943, (2 folders)
    - Letters from the public, 1942-1943
  - Keegan v. United States, letters from the public, 1945 (Box 81)
  - Marshall of the Court, 1927-1928, 1942-1944
  - Minersville School District v. Gobitis
    - Clippings, 1940
    - Letters from the public, 1940, (2 folders)
  - Miscellaneous cases
    - Clippings
    - Letters from the public, 1932-1944
  - New Supreme Court building
    - Gilbert, Cass, 1927-1936
    - Lynn, David, 1934-1936
    - Miscellaneous, 1926-1936
  - Office procedures
  - Procedure revisions
    - 1934, Mar.-1935
    - 1935-1936, Apr.
  - Reporter of the court
    - 1925-1927
    - 1928-1929
    - 1930-1933 (Box 82)
    - 1934-1936
    - 1937-1938
    - 1939
    - 1940-1941
  - Roberts letter, 1942
  - Rogers v. Guaranty Trust Co., letters from the public, 1933
  - Rule revisions
  - Schneiderman v. United States, letter from the public
  - Statistical and historical materials
  - United States v. Local 807, 1942
    - Clippings
    - Letters from the public
  - United States v. Butler, letters from the public, 1936
  - Viereck v. United States, 1943
    - Clippings
    - Letters from the public
  - Waller, Odell, letters from the public, 1942
  - West Publishing Co.
  - West Virginia School Board v. Barnette, clippings, 1943
  - Writs of error, 1928
- Miscellany, 1907-1953 (Box 83-87)
  Biographer's papers, greeting cards, notes, speeches and writings, menus, certificates, clippings, printed matter, and other material.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Biographer's papers (Box 83)
  - Briefs prior to 1925, (6 folders); (5 folders) (Box 84)
    - (annotated)
  - Certificates and oaths (Box 85)
  - Dinner table seatings
  - Financial papers
  - Greeting cards and snapshots
  - In re Wiltinger Schlangengraben 1933 (wine party)
  - Invitations
  - Judicial appointments of Theodore Roosevelt (photocopy of letter from Roosevelt to Mark Sullivan, 1907, May 13 )
  - Letters of recommendation from Amherst College professors, Amherst, Mass., 1894
  - Menus, (2 folders)
  - Newspaper clippings
    - Mrs. Harlan Fiske Stone
    - Stone's appointment as chief justice
    - Stone's appointment to the Court
    - Stone's death, (3 folders); (7 folders) (Box 86)
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
  - Notes, poems, and other unidentified writings (Box 87)
  - Opinions and other unidentified legal material
  - Opinions which came down on the day of Stone's death
  - Partnership agreement with William Nelson Cromwell, 1923, June
  - Printed matter
    - Congressional Record, 1925, Feb. 5
    - “Stone Reference Portfolio”
    - General
  - Recipes
  - Speeches and articles by and about Stone
  - Trust fund agreement, 1916
  - Will of Agnes Harvey Stone
  - Wine labels
  - Wine lists